Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 2)
  - Research Dept
    - Planning/Research CL-7 Statistical Report
      - Southeast Region, 2/1972-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - Mid-Atlantic Region Region, 3/1972-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 43)
      - Northeast Region, 2/1972-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 44)
      - 1971 Xeroxed Copies, Southeast, Mid-Atlantic, and Northeast Regions, 2/1970-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 45)
      - Total Income 1970 Affiliates, circa 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - 1971 Xeroxed Copies, Western and Southwest Regions, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - 1971 Xeroxed Copies, Midwest and Great Lakes Region, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - CL-7's 1971 Worksheets, circa 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - 1970 Books I-III, Western/Southwest/Midwest/Great Lakes/Southeast/Mid-Atlantic/Northeast Regions, circa 1970 (Box 72, Folder 5-7)
      - Reports Midwest, Great Lakes, Southeast, Mid-Atlantic, Northeast, Western, and Southwestern Regions for 1969 and 1969 CL-7 Forms, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 8-11)
      - Forms, 1968, Alabama, Montana, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Reports Birmingham, AL, Saginaw, MI, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Reports Minneapolis, MN, Youngstown, OH, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - 1968, Pennsylvania, Wisconsin, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Reports, Muskogee, OK, Milwaukee, WI, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - 1968 As Is from T. Tsuruoka, Received Central Records 1977, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - 1968 Patient Load, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Reports Alabama-Wisconsin, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
      - 1967, As Is from T. Tsuruoka, Received Central Records, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - 1966 As Is from T. Tsuruoka, Received Central Records, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - 1966 Forms Alabama, New Mexico, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - 1966 Omnibus Reports New York, Wisconsin, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - 1965 Forms Alabama-Wisconsin, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
      - 1965 Vital Statistics, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - 1964 Moster, Vital Statistics, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - 1964 Omnibus, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Omnibus Reports 1963, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - 1963 Summary of Data Final, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - 1962 Master & Summary of Data, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - 1962 Omnibus Reports, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Omnibus Questionnaires 1961, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - 1961 Master Sample, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Master, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Omnibus Report 1960, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Omnibus Questionnaires 1959, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - 1959 Master, circa 1960 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Omnibus Questionnaires 1958, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - 1958 Master (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - 1957 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Planning & Evaluation
    - Affiliate Evaluation Policies & Procedures, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Director of Planning & Evaluation, Johnson, Jane M., Appointment, 5/8/1979-7/30/1979 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Jane, Correspondence, 7/12/1979-1/19/1981 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation Protocol & Methodology, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Service Report, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Service Data, 4/1/1980-1/1981 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Fertility Rates, 3/8/1977-3/13/1978 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Affiliates' Annual Report, Statistics & General, 2/24/1961-2/27/1973 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - 1971 Total Pat. Figures As Is from T. Tsuruoka, 6/8/1972-8/14/1972 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Tables, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - CL-7 Charts, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Medical Services Provided by Affiliates, Original, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Production Time Reports As Is from T. Tsuruoka, 2/28/1969-6/30/1971 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - CL-7 1970 Percent of New Patients Below 20 Years of Age, Classification by Size of Total Contraceptive Case Load, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - NCHS, Tsuruoka As Is from T. Tsuruoka Received Central Records 1977, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - CL-7 NCSH, 5/1973 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Research Dept
    - Affiliate Abortion Survey, 3/8/1973 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Analysis of Gov't Grants by Size of Affiliates, 10/20/1971 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Attitudes Toward Overpopulation & Family Planning, 12/1970 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - CL-2, CL-2A, CL-16, 4/2/1973 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 9/26/1967-10/31/1974 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - A Do-It-Yourself Guide, circa 1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Rachel Boaz Situation, 8/27/1971-5/8/1972 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Clinic Evaluation Services, 4/19/1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Clinic Cost Study, 7/1/1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Clinic Profiles, Family Planning: Clinic & Cost Evaluation (H-168-1R2), 6/29/1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Clinic Service Definitions, 5/18/1972 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Cost/Manpower Study, Philadelphia, 7/1972 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Dryfoos, Polgar, Varky Formula, 3/24/1972 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Final Report to the Division of Research DHEW, Grant No. MC-R-360055-04-0 1972, 12/1972-1/12/1973 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Family Planning: Clinic & Cost Evaluation (H-168-1R2) Reports 1, 2, 3, 2/20/1970-5/4/1970 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Family Planning Cross Sectional Clinic Cost Study: A Preliminary Report Children's Bureau (H-168-1R2), circa 1970 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Summary Report on Project H-168-1R2 Family Planning: Clinic & Cost Evaluation, circa 1970 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Family Planning Cross Sectional Clinic Cost Study, Proposal to HEW, 4/4/1968 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - General, Mimeos, 3/3/1970-3/11/1974 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Research, General, 3/21/1968-10/30/1968 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Grants, 1/19/1971-9/24/1971 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Guides for Clinic Managers, 2/1974-9/1974 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Medical Student, Teen Survey, Correspondence, 4/26/1971 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Information on NCHS Patients Records System, 10/2/1970 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Job Descriptions (S. Polgar), 4/3/1967 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Family Planning in Dallas, An Approach to Development & Coordination of Services, 7/1968 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Methodological, 6/10/1968-10/15/1968 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Mobile Service Demonstration Project, 5/17/1972-8/29/1972 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Attitudes Toward Overpopulation & Family Planning, 12/1970 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - National Analysts
      - Attitudes Towards Overpopulation & Family Planning, 12/1970 (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Evaluation of Advertising Prototypes, 4/1971 (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Evaluation of Advertising Prototypes, 2/1971 (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - Motivational Research, 11/19/1969-1/22/1971 (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - A Program of Research Directed at Population Control, 10/1969 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Research Proposal, 2/23/1970 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - National Center Health Statistics from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - 1975 (Box 75)
    - NCHS Patient Record System Memos, Mimeos, General from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - 1975 (Box 75)
    - National Center Health Statistics Workshops, 11/17/1971-12/7/1971 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Revised Agency Use Section of NCHS Clinic Visit Record 1974-1976
      - 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - 1975 (Box 75)
    - Instructors, Revised Agency Use Section of NCHS Clinic Visit Record, 11/12/1974, [no folders 36-38] (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - National Youth Survey, 3/24/1972-3/29/1972 (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Newark Occupational Settings Project Progress Report #s 3-5 Contract # HMS 110-73-393, 5/22/1973-6/24/1974 (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 7/22/1970-10/15/1970 (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - On-Site Evaluations for St. Louis Metropolitan Area Council for Voluntary Family Planning, 7/11/1972-4/3/1973 (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - Organization Chart, Outline Research Activities, Closing the Gap Diagram, 7/1970 (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - Patient Follow-Up Study, Preliminary Report (Polgar), 7/22/1963 (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - the Population Problem, A Global View George Varky, 9/30/1967 (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Population Seminars, 11/14/1969-12/3/1969 (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Project Proposals, 2/17/1969-3/29/1974 (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Progress Reports, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - Proposed Plan, Research Strategy Comm. Population, Family Planning, Contraceptives, 1/29/1971 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Public Opinion & Abortion Reform Summary of Opinion Survey, 5/8/1972 (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Public Opinion, Population & Family Planning, Richard Pomeroy & Morton Silver, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Research, Affiliates Clinics, 7/17/1967-2/27/1969 (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - The Quest for Fertility Control: A Program of Research, 7/1955 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Region IV Plan, Existing Programs as Models, 4/19/1972 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - RFP of Cost Accounting, HSA/Dhew, 4/25/1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Research Project on Adoption, 7/1970 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Research Prospectus for an Experiment in Family Services in Low Income Neighborhood in NYC, 4/1/1965 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Review of Major Activities, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - SDA Workshops, 11/29/1971-11/30/1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - SDA Corporation Correspondence & General, 8/9/1972-4/18/1974 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Staff Attitude Questionnaire with Multiple Personal Inventory Form, 9/5/1969 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Status of SMSA Communities, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Status Report Research Dept Fiscal Year 1974 Funding Possibilities, 6/1/1973 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Study of Abortion, Related Family Planning Services, NY Law Reform, 4/29/1971-7/1/1971 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Studies of Patient Drop-Outs from FP Clinics. Low Income Neighborhood Surveys of Women of Child Bearing Ages. Grand Rapids And Albuquerque Surveys, circa 1970 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Summary Position Paper Affiliate Participation In Services Delivery, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Survey of Contraceptive Counseling in Facilities Providing Abortions, N.Y. State, 5/19/1972 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Surveys, Miscellaneous, 1/6/1972-1/11/1973 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Survey, Recent Trends in Public Support of Liberalized Abortion Laws and Birth Control Information and Services for Unmarried, 10/15/1972 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Unmet Need Data by PPFA Affiliate Turf, 8/15/1975-10/8/1975 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Clinics A User's Guide, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - STAFF
      - Polgar, S., Continuing Responsibilities with PPFA after 9/1/67, 7/13/1967 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Renaud, Frank, Correspondence and Memos, 10/7/1971 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Renaud, Francis, Report Planning, 4/14/1971-7/17/1972 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Morton Silver, Gen. Correspondence
        - 1970-1974 (Box 76, Folder 23)
        - 1975 (Box 76)
      - Morton Silver, Birth Control and the Private Physician, 2/24/1972 (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Morton Silver, Providing Family Planning Services at Industrial Settings, 1/17/1975 (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - Dr. Eleanor Snyder, General Correspondence, 12/15/1969-2/8/1974 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - The Uniform Family Planning Reporting System, 5/1/1969 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Resources Dept
    - Alden, Dana, Correspondence, circa 1980 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Arlow, Phyllis, Correspondence, circa 1980 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Affiliates Fund Raising
      - Evants, John H. Assistant Director, 2/24/1971-7/30/1971 (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - Emily Freeman, Director, 1/21/1970-11/19/1970 (Box 76, Folder 31)
      - Emily Freeman, Director, 8/16/1968-12/29/1969 (Box 76, Folder 32)
      - Emily Freeman, Affiliates Campaign, 6/1968 (Box 76, Folder 33)
      - Emily Freeman, Affiliates Campaign Report, 9/1970 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Gilpatric, Affiliate Contributions to Field Dept. Emergency Fund, 7/8/1971-8/16/1971 (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Fund Raising Bibliographies, circa 1980 (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Affiliate Contributions to the PPWP "Emergency Fund" Memphis Challenge, 5/15/1971-2/22/1972 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Affiliate Fund Raising, Allocation From U.F. and Dues Budgeted/Permitted 1971-1972, circa 1972 (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Affiliate Fund Raising Booklet, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Affiliate Fund Raising
      - Deduction For Fund Raising Staff Member, 11/1977 (Box 76, Folder 40)
      - Deduction of Loan for Fund Raising Staff Member, 1/1975 (Box 76, Folder 41)
      - Demonstration Project, 12/1/1972 (Box 76, Folder 42)
      - Fair Share Report Forms, circa 1973 (Box 76, Folder 43)
      - Joint Solicitations, 10/1973 (Box 76, Folder 44)
      - Gilpatric, M., Regional Totals, 6/10/1971 (Box 76, Folder 45)
      - Gilpatric, United Fund, 1/1973-11/8/1974 (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Affiliate Income Chart 1969-1977, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Fair Share Chart, 11/17/1980 & 12/4/1980 (Box 76, Folder 48)
    - 15 Affiliates Which Made Highest Dues Payments in 1970. Contributions and Dues Paid For 1966-1971, circa 1970 (Box 76, Folder 49)
    - The Fund Raising Campaign, 3/10/1980 (Box 76, Folder 50)
    - Gilpatric, Fund Raising Workshops, 3/1977-1/21/1980 (Box 76, Folder 51)
    - Fund Raising, A PP work kit, circa 1975 (Box 76, Folder 52)
    - Gilpatric, Marguerite, Memos, Mimeos, General, from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 53)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 76)
    - Affiliate Fund Raising, Gilpatric Marguerite, from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 54)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 76)
    - Guidelines for Affiliate Loan Fund, 3/1970 (Box 76, Folder 55)
    - How to Raise Money For Your Affiliate, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 56)
    - List of Affiliate Staff Fund Raisers, 8/1978 (Box 76, Folder 57)
    - Gilpatric, M., Mimeos to Affiliate Fund Raisers from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 58)
      - circa 1975-1976 (Box 76)
    - The Fund Raiser, A Newsletter, 5/1977-8/1979 (Box 76, Folder 59)
    - Gilpatric, M., Rebates/ Deductions
      - 1974 (Box 76, Folder 60)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
    - Gilpatric, M., Seminars, 3/25/1974 (Box 76, Folder 61)
    - Total Private Voluntary Contribution to PP Affiliates and Dues Paid to PPWP 1966-1971, 11/29/1971 (Box 76, Folder 62)
    - 1964 Income Reported By Affiliates in Omnibus and Fund Raising Reports, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 63)
    - Omnibus 1977, 10/16/1978 (Box 76, Folder 64)
    - Omnibus 1976, 7/1977 (Box 76, Folder 65)
    - Omnibus 1975, 6/1976 (Box 76, Folder 66)
    - Omnibus 1974, 6/1975 (Box 76, Folder 67)
    - Omnibus 1973, circa 1974 (Box 76, Folder 68)
    - Omnibus 1972, circa 1973 (Box 76, Folder 69)
    - Omnibus 1971, circa 1972 (Box 76, Folder 70)
    - Omnibus 1970, circa 1971 (Box 76, Folder 71)
    - Omnibus, Correspondence, 5/5/1976-8/14/1978 (Box 76, Folder 72)
    - The Optional Plan For Sharing (TOPS), 7/13/1979 (Box 76, Folder 73)
    - Proposed Fair Share Assessments, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 74)
    - Affiliate Fund Raising Resources, Status of Loans and Deductions for Fund Raising Staff Members, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 75)
    - Alan F. Guttmacher Memorial Fund, 5/13/1974-8/13/1974 (Box 76, Folder 76)
    - Analysis of 1970/1971 Unrestricted Revenue by Category Compared w/ Fund Raising Exp., 10/19/1971 (Box 76, Folder 77)
    - American Film Theater Benefit, 12/1/1972-7/10/1973 (Box 76, Folder 78)
    - Benefits, Miscellaneous from 1972
      - 1972 (Box 76, Folder 79)
      - 1977 (Box 76)
    - Bequests and Deferred Gifts
      - Estate of Francis Alpert from 1979 (Paul, Eve), 1/9/1979 (Box 76, Folder 80)
      - Financial Data, 10/11/1972 (Box 76, Folder 81)
      - Survey, 7/15/1975 (Box 76, Folder 82)
      - Bequest Forms, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 83)
      - Legal Resources, (Paul, E.), 5/5/1978-8/2/1979 (Box 76, Folder 84)
      - 1/6/1975-3/1980 (Box 76, Folder 85-86)
      - 2/17/1972-12/17/1974 (Box 76, Folder 87)
      - Bulletin, 2/1972-4/1973 (Box 76, Folder 88)
      - General, 1/26/1955-11/10/1971 (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
      - General, 11/28/1951 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - McCormick Bequest Recommendations for the Employment of the Money. Ad Hoc Committee, Exec. and Board Minutes
        - 1969-1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 77)
      - McCormick Bequest Documents, Will Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 77)
      - Phillip's Bequest from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 77, Folder 6)
        - 1975 (Box 77)
      - Potential Testamentary Funding of Abortion Program for Unmarried Women, 9/13/1973-11/19/1973 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Resolution on Bequests and Deferred Gifts, 8/8/1973-5/10/1974 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Waldorf Estates Wills, Citations, Etc., 6/1/1964-2/8/1965 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Waldorf Estates Correspondence, 1/2/1957-7/22/1969 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Estate of Williams, Bernardt, 7/18/1958-8/5/1959 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Estate of Verity, Walter, M.D., 3/25/1959-7/24/1959 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Business and the Birth Rate, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Businessman, Planned Parenthood and The Wachsmuth, 3/1955-7/1955 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - The Businessmen's Stake in P.P., by Pierre S. duPont 3rd, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Businessman's Stake In the Population Problem, Address by James F. Oates, Jr., 6/1966 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Population Growth: Boon? - Or Calamity? Economic Analysis Section, AT&T Co., 7/1971 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Adolph W. Schmidt. The Businessman's Stake, 1/1968 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Businessman and the Population Problem, 12/22/1969 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 8/1978 & 1/18/1979 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Employee Campaigns from 1973
      - 1973 (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 77)
    - Employee Campaign from 1972
      - 1972, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - 1975, 1979 (Box 77)
    - Federal Services Campaign, International Service Agency
      - Legal (Paul, Eve), 1/24/1979 & 6/7/1979 (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 77)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - 1977 (Box 77)
      - Application for Certification
        - 1969-1970, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 77)
    - Campaign Foundation Appeals, 6/1/1970-12/18/1970 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Fund Raising Campaign, General, 10/1972-11/1972 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - The Fund Raising Game, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Campaign Fund Raising Consultants, Richard Beckhard Associates, 10/1967 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Campaign 1972, Fund Raising Materials for Affiliates, 10/1971 (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Campaign, Nationwide
      - General Correspondence
        - 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 32)
        - 1978 (Box 77)
        - 1963-1969 (Box 77, Folder 33-34)
      - Advertising, 1963-1968 (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Movie, Correspondence, 11/20/1963-6/23/1968 (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Paul Calabi, 8/31/1967-6/14/1968 (Box 77, Folder 37)
      - Midwest Region, Kansas City, Missouri, 2/24/1964-6/30/1964 (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - Southwest Region, Dallas, Texas, 1/27/1964-6/30/1964 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - Western Region, Los Angeles, CA, 2/19/1964-6/11/1964 (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Campaign Fund Raising, Pharmaceutical Houses, 1/15/1963-1/23/1970 (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Proposal For A Margaret Sanger Centennial Campaign, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - UPP CAMPAIGN
      - 1/20/1970-12/20/1972 (Box 77, Folder 43)
      - Foundation Report, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 44)
      - Fund Raising Analysis and Evaluation Bowen and Gurin and Barnes, Inc., 12/1967 (Box 77, Folder 45)
      - 1973-1975 Fund Raising Comparison, 4/28/1976 (Box 77, Folder 46)
      - Lists of Invites to Serve on Board of Financial Trustees and Advisory Board, 8/13/1970 (Box 77, Folder 47)
      - Loan to PPNYC, 4/28/1972 (Box 77, Folder 48)
      - Major Documents, 2/1969-8/2/1972 (Box 77, Folder 49)
      - Midyear Report, 8/25/1978 (Box 77, Folder 50)
      - PP Campaign, NYC, 1/11/1978 (Box 77, Folder 51)
      - PPWP/UPPC Negotiations 1974/1975, 2/28/1974-6/17/1974 (Box 77, Folder 52)
      - Origins of UPPC, 12/3/1969 (Box 77, Folder 53)
      - "Outline of the UPPC" (draft), Kingsley, 1/21/1977 (Box 77, Folder 54)
      - Annual Report, 3/3/1971 (Box 77, Folder 55)
      - Analysis of NYC Donations Cal. Yr., 1967 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Budget 1979, Comparison 1978 vs. 1979 PPFA's Program, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Budget and Distribution Statements from 1969
        - 1970-1974 (Box 78, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 78)
      - Campaign Cabinet Mtg. Minutes, 4/28/1976 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Contributions of $1000 and over, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - 1/30/1975-4/26/1977 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - 1974 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - 1975 (Box 78)
      - 1/3/1973-12/17/1973 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Philanthropic Priorities: The Case for Family Planning, 5/1973 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - PPWP/PPNYC Agreement from 1969
        - 1968-1974 (Box 78, Folder 10)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 78)
      - Revised Table Showing UPPC Results 1969-1972, 1/8/1973 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Steering Committee, 12/8/1969-11/18/1970 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Steering Committee, Minutes, 2/9/1970-6/23/1970 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Table of World Wide Expenditures, Calendar Year, 6/1974 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - General, 1/1968-11/1971 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Campaign Income 1971-1975, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Campaign Structure (proposed), 11/7/1969 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Direct Mail Costs, 2/12/1974 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - West Virginia Test Campaign, 5/18/1973 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Contributions, Charitable Contribution of Services, Legal Opinion, 7/6/1964-3/31/1972 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Charitable Fund Raising Act, NJ Fund Raisers Registration Form, 10/29/1975-11/4/1975 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Charitable Organization Report, 1/5/1978 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Colloquy, 8/1977 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Commerce and Industry from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 78, Folder 24)
      - 1975, 1978 (Box 78)
    - Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. Report PPFA, 8/1978 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Contributions and Gifts
      - Contribution Analysis Report, 5/1975 (Box 78, Folder 26)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 78, Folder 27)
      - 1969-1974 (Box 78, Folder 28-29)
      - Contributors' Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 78, Folder 30)
        - 1975, 1977, 1980 (Box 78)
      - List and Analysis Contributors, 1966-1970 (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Tax Deductible, U.S. Treasury Dept., Internal Revenue, 1/26/1972 (Box 78, Folder 32)
      - The Cost of Fund Raising, Sweezy, 1974-1975 (Box 78, Folder 33)
      - Major Donors List from 1969
        - 1972 (Box 78, Folder 34)
        - 1978 (Box 78)
      - Gifts, 9/2/1965-1/22/1969 (Box 78, Folder 35)
      - Craver, Mathews, Smith & Co. (Centralization of Donor Lists), 12/1978 (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Critz, Doris, 4/12/1976-5/23/1977 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Direct Mail Agreement, PPFA, LAPP, Pasadena PP and Western Region, 2/20/1973-5/7/1973 (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Direct Mail, Income Procedures, 2/1971 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Direct Mail, Management Survey Final Report, 5/4/1978 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - The Dollars Saved by Family Planning Programs, 10/1974 (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Facts from Giving USA 1974 American Association of Fund Raising Council, 7/23/1974 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Fair Share
      - Plan, 12/1977-1/1980 (Box 78, Folder 43)
      - 1977 Preliminary Figures, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 44)
      - Revision of the Fair Share Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 78, Folder 45-46)
      - Chart for 1974 - $1 Million, 10/1973 (Box 78, Folder 47)
      - Plan, 9/8/1972 (Box 78, Folder 48)